There is a lot of oatmeal, a lot of salt and some water.
Sticky
It should be sticky, yes.
Good as well.
It is very ...
Hard, sticky, heavy.
Extremely disgusting.
Salt.
It should taste salt as well.
Then you just pour.
It is terrible.
It's like.
Now you were central to the stuff, then the skis follow the ground.
Now you have been selected for the World Cup.
How did you think then
It feels too good to be true.
It's great fun and I
Feel that I am here to create experience.
If I manage to ride the skiing I know I can go
Then I will be really happy but I have not set up -
Some results.
Should I give some tips ...
so is it to take advantage of
Partly that it is home and ...